represent.com 2018-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Represent

_Last updated on May 28, 2018_

Represent Holdings, LLC (“Represent”, “we”, “our” or “us”) understands that privacy is important to our website users and customers. This Privacy Policy sets out how we will collect and use the personal information you provide to us while using the website located at www.represent.com (the “Site”) and/or the services provided from it (the “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Site and the Services. It does not apply to any other site, product or service of Represent, its affiliates, third party sellers, or customers.

By accessing or using the Site, you are deemed to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not access or otherwise use the Site or Services. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be posted on the Site. We encourage you to periodically review the Site for the latest information on our privacy practices.

The Site, together with all its content, is owned or controlled by Represent Holdings, LLC, a company headquartered in California, USA with its office at 1680 Vine St., #400, Los Angeles, CA 90028.

## PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

To provide the Site and the Services, we may collect and process certain personal information that you voluntarily submit to us, such as through our contact pages, by email, by seeking employment with us, by creating an account on the Site, by making purchases on the Site or some other means. We take care to keep this information secure and prevent any unauthorized access or unlawful use of it as described in the “Security” section below.

The personal information you may provide to us could include your name, address, date of birth, gender, email addresses and/or mobile phone numbers, and financial information such as credit/debit card numbers.

## NON-PERSONAL OR AGGREGATE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we may automatically collect certain non-identifying information about you, such as the type of browser or device operating system you use, the domain name of the website from which you linked to us, the amount of time you spend on the Site and the pages on the Site that you view. We may also aggregate information collected from our users (such as the number of users in a particular region or having particular characteristics).

## INFORMATION USAGE

The information we collect about you or you provide to us will be used to provide you with the Services and any other services associated with them.

In addition, we may use your personal information:

  * To respond to your direct queries.
  * To operate the Site and to provide you with any specific services that you have requested.
  * To add you to our mailing lists and to send you emails from time to time.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To create profiles to help us analyze or predict your personal preferences or interests for marketing purposes.
  * To save and identify your product designs on the Site.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please let us know as described in the “Opt-Out Process” section below.

You may withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information at any time by contacting us at [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com); however, in that event, we may be unable to provide our Services to you.

## INFORMATION SHARING

We may disclose and market aggregated information about users of our Services, and aggregated information collected via our Services, that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We will only share your personal information as described below, unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personal information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you.

We may disclose your personal information:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Represent's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Represent about our users is among the assets transferred.
  * Subject to applicable laws, to the organizers of a Represent campaign and other third parties, to allow them to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep your personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see the “Opt-Out Process” section below.
  * To fulfill any purpose for which you provide it.
  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our contract terms and conditions, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * To investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the policies for the Site.

## INTEREST BASED ADVERTISING

We may directly or through a third party vendor use non-personally identifiable information in connection with our own or our vendors’ information to display or deliver targeted advertising to you on our Site and to manage our advertising on other sites. Cookies, clickstream data, web beacons and other similar technologies may be used to collect information in order to provide personalized advertising. For example, if you are searching for information on a particular product, we or our vendors may cause an advertisement to appear on other websites you view with information on that product. This form of advertising, sometimes called “interest based advertising,” is based on anonymous information and not on any personal information. As a result, we and our vendors know your interests, but do not personally identify you in connection with the delivery of that specific ad. We believe that such advertising is helpful because you will see advertisements that are relevant to your interests. However, if you would like to opt-out of these interest-based advertisements, please follow the opt-out process described below under “Interest Based Advertising Opt-Out.”

## COOKIES

We may place small data files on your device or device hard drive known as “cookies” or a similar type of file (such as clear gifs, web beacons, tags, etc.) for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with the Site. Many websites use cookies for these purposes. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information. We use this information internally, to help us maintain and enhance the efficiency and usefulness of the Site. We may also use and place cookies on your device from our third party service providers in connection with the Site, such as an analytics provider that helps us manage and analyze Site usage. We also use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. Our persistent cookies may remain active on your device for up to 1-3 years (depending upon the purpose of the cookie) or until you delete them manually. We set a persistent cookie to enable us to track and target the interests of users to enhance the services we provide. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve personal information from your device without your knowledge. If you do not wish to receive cookies or want to restrict them or flush them from your device, you may do so by changing the settings on your computer or browser accordingly, in which case you may still use our Site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

## CLICKSTREAM DATA

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a website’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of device and browsing software you use and the address of the website from which you linked to the Site. We may collect and use clickstream data to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on websites, how visitors navigate throughout websites and how we may tailor our Site to better meet consumer needs. This information will be used to improve our Site and our Services. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous, and will not intentionally contain any personal data.

## SECURITY

We have implemented technical and organizational measures, appropriate to the risk, to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and unauthorized disclosure or access. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information provided online.

## DATA RETENTION

We retain your personal information, if provided by you through the Site, for as long as your inquiry is active (as determined by us) and for a reasonable time thereafter, or if applicable, for as long as you remain on our marketing list. We also may retain your personal information for a longer period of time on the basis of our legitimate interests in providing our Services to you or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Even if we delete some or all of your personal information, we may continue to retain and use aggregated or anonymous data previously collected so that it can no longer be used for personal identification and/or anonymize or aggregate your personal information. Please note that we will not be liable for disclosures of your data due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.

## OTHER SITES

As a convenience to you, we may provide links to third party websites from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third party sites, and by providing a link we are not endorsing or promoting such third party sites. When you link away from our Site, you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to read the policies and terms of every website you visit.

## SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICES

The Site may integrate with social networking services. You understand that we do not control such services and are not liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Site, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are relying upon those third party services to operate properly and fairly.

You should be aware that personal information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

## INFORMATION RELATING TO CHILDREN

Our Site is designed for those 13 years of age and older. We do not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have received such information, or any information in violation of this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to locate and remove that information from our records. In the case of residents of the European Union, we do not collect information from anyone under the age of 16 except with parental consent, subject to an EU member state providing by law for a lower age (not below 13 years).

## COMMUNICATIONS WITH REPRESENT

By providing your email address to us, you expressly consent to receive emails from us. We may use email to communicate with you, to send information that you have requested or to send information about other services provided by us, provided that, we will not give your email address to another party to promote their products or services directly to you except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## OPT-OUT PROCESS

If you do not want your personal information shared with any third party who may use such information for direct marketing purposes, then send an email to [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com) stating that you want to opt-out of such disclosures. However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided with your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

If you receive a promotional email from us, you may unsubscribe from promotional emails through a link, typically at the bottom of the email.

As noted above, you may opt-out of or restrict the placement of cookies on your device or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on many mobile devices. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

If you do not want us to use your personal information for our marketing purposes, send us an email at [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com) stating that you withdraw your consent to such use.

## INTEREST BASED ADVERTISING OPT-OUT

We may, and may work with third parties, to use non-personal information to deliver targeted advertisements to you based upon your online activities and other information. The online advertising industry provides a service through which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from certain data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. We comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising set forth by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can opt-out of targeted advertising from certain providers at www.aboutads.info/consumers.

Please note that by opting out, you will continue to see generic advertising that is not tailored to your specific interests and activities. To be clear, whether you are using our opt-out or an online industry opt-out, these cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted out on your device browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device.

## DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS

Please note that we do not respond to or honor “do not track” signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. The information we collect from you through the Service may be transferred to, stored at, and processed in the USA and other destinations outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or other country in which you are located. This includes processing by us, our affiliates, our third party service companies and other third parties as described in the “Information Usage” and “Information Sharing” sections above. You explicitly consent and agree to such transfer, storing and/or processing of your personal information outside the EEA or other country in which you are located. You understand that data stored in the USA may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the USA. The USA may not have data protection laws that are as comprehensive or protective as those in your country of residence; however, our collection, storage and use of your personal information will at all times be in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## YOUR EUROPEAN UNION PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a resident of the European Union, you have certain additional rights with respect to your personal information under the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (the “GDPR”), including the following:

  * The right of access to your personal information.
  * The right to rectify your personal information if it is incorrect or incomplete.
  * The right to have your personal information erased (“right to be forgotten”) if certain grounds are met.
  * The right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information at any time (if our processing is based on consent).
  * The right to object to our processing of your personal information (if processing is based on legitimate interests).
  * The right to object to our processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
  * The right to receive your personal information from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and the right to transmit your personal information to another controller without hindrance from us (data portability).

If you are located in the European Union and you are or have been our customer, we may send you marketing communications based on our legitimate interests, subject always to your right to opt out of such communications. Further, if you are located in the European Union, we will never share your personal information with a third party for such third party’s marketing purposes, unless you have specifically consented to us doing so.

You may contact us at [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com) to exercise any of the above rights. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity, and in some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your personal information. Furthermore, if you believe that our processing of your personal information is inconsistent with your data protection rights under the GDPR and we have not adequately addressed your concerns, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority of your country.

For purposes of the GDPR, we are a “controller” and you are a “data subject.”

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law permits customers in California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for those third parties’ own direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you may request such information from us by contacting us by email at [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com). Any such request must include "California Privacy Rights Request" in the first line of the description and include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.

## QUESTIONS AND COMMENTS

If you have any queries or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted-out of receiving, please contact us at [support@represent.com](mailto:support@represent.com).
